Support for NPR Music comes from Capital
NPR Music 得到了 Capital
One, proud supporters of NPR Music and
One 的支持，Capital One 是 NPR Music 和
the Tiny Desk Contest. What's in your
Tiny Desk Contest 的忠实支持者。 你的钱包里有什么
wallet? Learn more at capitalone.com.
？ 了解更多信息，请访问 capitalone.com。
&gt;&gt; Ladies and gentlemen, I go by the name
女士们先生们，我的名字是
Ayra [music] Starr.
艾拉·斯塔尔（Ayra Starr）。
All the way from Lagos, Nigeria.
来自尼日利亚拉各斯。
I run out of shots, I run out of myself.
我的生命耗尽了，我也耗尽了自己。
I run out of luck, so I run out of
运气用完了，我的精力也就耗尽了
myself. Money make the rain come, I'mma
。 金钱能让雨水落下，我
take some. I can make the rain come,
要拿一些。 我可以祈雨，
mama take some. [singing and music]
妈妈拿一些吧。  [歌声和音乐]
You can't be too worried about what's me
你不必太担心我。
I. I learned to be gangster right from
我就是从
these dark times. I release my mind, I
这些黑暗的日子里学会了如何当个狠角色。 我放松身心，
need to re-up. I dare a [__] to say
需要补充能量。 我倒要看看哪个婊子敢说三道四
some. [__] up up my face
。 搞砸我的脸
[singing and music] down. Crying through
[唱歌和音乐]下来。 隔着
a window. I want love some.
窗户哭泣。 我想要一些爱。
I heard a bird sing. Come outside.
我听到鸟儿在歌唱。 出来。
I run from my enemies. Peace [singing]
我逃离敌人。 内心的平静（歌唱）
of my mind.
。   一场争夺
War for my energy.
我能量的战争。
No, no.
不，不。
[__] can you wrap it up when you talk
贱人，你
to me now? I don't watch my tone cuz I
现在跟我说话能不能长点心？ 我不注意自己的语气，因为我
like how I sound. Delete you off my
喜欢自己的声音。 现在就把你从我的
phone now, I need some new energy.
手机里删除，我需要一些新的能量。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Energy.
能量。
My mother told me giving up is giving
我妈妈告诉我放弃就是
up, so [singing] I made another way.
放弃，所以我唱着歌，另辟蹊径。
I told my [__] hold me down, hold me
我告诉我的姐妹们，帮我撑住，帮我
down cuz these [__] are a play.
撑住，因为这些家伙都是骗子。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; I run my city, run my life, run my mind,
我掌控我的城市，掌控我的人生，掌控我的思想，
but I never run away.
但我从不逃离。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; I'm so careful with my energy. Please,
我很珍惜我的精力。 请
never speak up on my name.
不要再提起我的名字。
This is Give Me That,
这是《给我那个》，一首
&gt;&gt; [music]
非常性感的歌曲，所以尽情扭动
your waist, okay?
你的腰肢吧，好吗？
Give me that love, Give me peace of
给我那份爱，给我内心的平静
mind. No shade, I call me with your
。 别误会，我只是表达你对我的
dislike.
厌恶而已。
I want that peace of mind where they
我想要那种安心的感觉，就像他们
come with that woo.
带着那种神秘感而来一样。
&gt;&gt; Where they come with that woo.
他们带着那种神秘感而来。
&gt;&gt; Baby, now I'm mad as we dey run. So,
宝贝，现在我们逃跑的时候我气疯了。 所以，
make you no [music] come waste time.
别浪费时间听音乐。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
No pressure. Make you give me that love.
别有压力。 让我得到你的爱。
If you give me me, I no go let go.
如果你把我给我，我绝不会放手。
Give me mega.
给我超级版。   快
&gt;&gt; Call my Santa Claus.
叫圣诞老人来。   一时
&gt;&gt; Feelings got me hitting on it.
冲动，我就这么做了。
&gt;&gt; Taking that floor. [singing]
占据那层楼。  [唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Make you give me that love. If you give
让我得到你的爱。 如果你把我给我
me me, I no go let go.
，我绝不会放手。
Give me mega.
给我超级版。
Feelings [music] got me hitting on it.
音乐让我情不自禁地投入其中。
&gt;&gt; Taking that floor.
占据那层楼。
&gt;&gt; Dialo, dialo.
Dialo, dialo.
If I give you my love, [singing] oh.
如果我把我的爱给你，[唱]哦。
Make you no disappoint, oh.
不会让你失望的，哦。
Me I got you for mind, oh.
我心里有你，哦。
Dialo, dialo. [singing]
Dialo, dialo.  [唱歌]
If I give you my love, oh.
如果我把我的爱给你，哦。
&gt;&gt; give you my love, oh.
把我的爱给你，哦。
&gt;&gt; Make you no disappoint,
不会让你失望，
[music and singing] oh.
[音乐和歌声]哦。
&gt;&gt; Make you no disappoint, oh.
不会让你失望的，哦。
&gt;&gt; Me I got you for mind, oh.
我心里有你，哦。
So many people want lick my stew. So,
好多人想舔我的炖菜。
baby, chill make I serve you, oh.
宝贝，别紧张，让我来为你服务，哦。
&gt;&gt; [music and singing]
[音乐和歌唱]
&gt;&gt; And if I and you are two by two, you fit
如果我们两个在一起，你很可能会
to fit to lose your cool.
失去冷静。
stars, oh my God.
我的天哪，很多原因都写在星辰之中。
So, baby, make you give me your love.
宝贝，让我感受到你的爱。
Make you give me that love.
让我得到你的爱。
If you give me me, I no go let go.
如果你把我给我，我绝不会放手。
Give me mega.
给我超级版。   快
&gt;&gt; Call my Santa Claus. [music]
叫圣诞老人来。  [音乐]
&gt;&gt; Feelings got me hitting on it.
情愫驱使我这么做。
&gt;&gt; Taking that floor.
占据那层楼。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Make you give me that love.
让我得到你的爱。
If you give me me, I
如果你把我给我，我
&gt;&gt; I no go let go.
绝不会放手。
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh. Make you give me mega.
嗯哼。 让我给你超级。   快
&gt;&gt; Call my Santa Claus. [singing]
叫圣诞老人来。  [唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Feelings got me hitting on it.
情愫驱使我去追求它。
&gt;&gt; Taking that floor.
占据那层楼。
&gt;&gt; Dialo, dialo.
Dialo, dialo.
If I give you my love, oh.
如果我把我的爱给你，哦。
&gt;&gt; If I give you [singing] my love, oh.
如果我把你[唱]我的爱给你，哦。
&gt;&gt; Make you no disappoint, oh.
不会让你失望的，哦。
&gt;&gt; Me I got you for mind, oh.
我心里有你，哦。
Dialo, dialo.
Dialo, dialo.
If I give you my love, oh.
如果我把我的爱给你，哦。
&gt;&gt; If [singing] make you no disappoint.
如果[唱歌]不会让你失望。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Fear got you by my dough.
恐惧让你落入我的口袋。
Hey.
嘿。
Come on. Hey.
快点。 嘿。
Go.
去。
Uh-huh.
嗯哼。
I said I should let you know
我说我应该让你知道
I love the way you did do me slow. Baby
我喜欢你温柔地对待我的方式。 宝贝，
cos I love me, [singing] you already
因为我爱我自己，[唱歌]你已经
know. Got every head turning. I see the
知道了。 吸引了所有人的目光。 我看到
press coming. So what you telling me
记者来了。 所以你现在想告诉我什么
now?
？
&gt;&gt; Who's that girl? Who's that girl?
那个女孩是谁？ 那个女孩是谁？   最近有
&gt;&gt; What's popping?
什么新鲜事？
&gt;&gt; Bad girl, there's no stopping.
坏女孩，你停不下来。
&gt;&gt; What's coming? Feeling the energy,
接下来会发生什么？ 感觉精力充沛，
adrenaline rushing. Real talk now, real
肾上腺素飙升。 说真的，
talk. They want to know. [singing]
说真的。 他们想知道。  [唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Who's that girl?
那女孩是谁？
&gt;&gt; I guess you never heard of me. I'm
看来你以前没听说过我。 我像
popping out like confetti.
五彩纸屑一样蹦了出来。
&gt;&gt; Who's that [singing] girl?
那个唱歌的女孩是谁？
&gt;&gt; Don't be clouding my energy cuz I'm the
别影响我的精力，因为
one they want to see.
他们想见的就是我。
&gt;&gt; I guess you never heard of me. I'm
看来你以前没听说过我。 我像
popping out like confetti. [singing]
五彩纸屑一样蹦了出来。  [唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Who's that girl?
那女孩是谁？
&gt;&gt; Don't be clouding my energy cuz I'm the
别影响我的精力，因为
one they want to see.
他们想见的就是我。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[歌唱]
[music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Smooth,
流畅，
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 像
&gt;&gt; flow like a river. If I catch beat that
河流般流淌。 如果我抓住节奏，
they won't panic [singing] be that.
他们就不会惊慌失措[唱歌]就是这样。
Cruise, Santa Monica. I demotivate like
圣莫尼卡游轮之旅。
cancer though [singing and music] we
虽然我们想要唱歌和音乐，但我却像癌症一样打击人们的积极性
want it. But the line moves. Fire like
。 但队伍在移动。 火如
Zeus. Carry my tools. If you get in my
宙斯。 帮我拿工具。 如果你能加入我的
empire great. Uh-huh. If you get in my
帝国，那就太好了。 嗯哼。 如果你能加入我的
empire great.
帝国，那就太好了。
Mhm. So what you telling me now?
嗯。 所以你现在想告诉我什么？
&gt;&gt; Who's that girl? Who's that girl?
那个女孩是谁？ 那个女孩是谁？   最近有
&gt;&gt; What's popping?
什么新鲜事？
&gt;&gt; Bad girl, there's no stopping.
坏女孩，你停不下来。
&gt;&gt; What's coming? Feeling the energy.
接下来会发生什么？ 感受到了这股能量。
Real talk
实话实说，
&gt;&gt; Real time.
实时对话。
&gt;&gt; They wanna know.
他们想知道。
&gt;&gt; Who's that girl?
那个女孩是谁？
&gt;&gt; I'm that girl.
我就是那个女孩。
&gt;&gt; Are you that girl?
你是那个女孩吗？
&gt;&gt; I'm that girl.
我就是那个女孩。
I say,
我说，
wait.
等等。
&gt;&gt; Na na [singing] na na na na na.
娜娜[唱歌]娜娜娜娜娜。
&gt;&gt; Na na na.
娜娜娜。
Na na na [music] na na.
娜娜娜 [音乐] 娜娜。
&gt;&gt; Na na na na na.
啦啦啦啦啦。
&gt;&gt; Na na na.
娜娜娜。
&gt;&gt; Na na na na [singing and music] na.
Na na na na [唱歌和音乐] na。
&gt;&gt; Na na [singing] na na na.
娜娜（唱歌）娜娜娜。
&gt;&gt; Ooh.
哦。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Yeah. YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
好。 是的。 是的。 是的。
&gt;&gt; OOH.
哦。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; THIS NEXT SONG IS MY next single. It's
下一首歌是我的下一首单曲。 它
called Tornado. And you're hearing it
叫龙卷风。 而且你是第一个听到这个消息的人
here first. It's [music] out June 12th.
。 这首歌将于6月12日发行。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Don't nobody care about your mula.
没人关心你的钱。
I'mma keep it straighter than a ruler.
我会把它弄得比尺子还直。
Who said that I'm a pretty mamacita?
谁说我是个漂亮辣妹？
So put some [music] eyes on me to keep
所以，请用音乐来让
me cooler. I know my diamonds wet like
我保持冷静。 我知道我的钻石像
scuba. Uh-huh. Everything blessed.
潜水服一样湿润。 嗯哼。 一切皆有祝福。
Hallelujah. Me and my girls in the club
哈利路亚。 我和我的姐妹们在夜店里
[music] like a doer. We chilling
像个行动派一样玩音乐。 我们
everyday.
每天都过得很放松。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; You can't wait to see me moving [music]
你迫不及待地想看到我随着节拍舞动 [音乐]
on the beat. Feel my [singing] fire
。 感受我心中燃烧的火焰，
heart and breathe. Press play then
然后呼吸。 按下播放键，然后倒带，
rewind repeat.
重复播放。
If they turn [singing] out the prize
如果他们能把唱歌变成
they wanna be. If you're starving,
他们想要的奖品。 如果你饿了，就让
[music] come and eat. I'm that girl they
音乐来填饱肚子吧。 我就是他们想成为的那种女孩，
when I hit
当我击中
You [singing] know you like it when I
你[唱]你知道你喜欢我的时候
You know you like it when I
你知道你喜欢我的时候
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱]
&gt;&gt; So we back, put your back in the corner.
所以我们回来了，把你的背靠在角落里。
I never wait for anybody. You know I
我从不等任何人。 你知道我
ain't just anybody. My body tea like
可不是一般人。 我的身体像喝了
bourbon. And I make a man fall in order.
波旁威士忌一样。 而我使人屈服。
If I tell you I won't come calling.
如果我告诉你，我就不会再来了。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; You better come and
你最好快来，
You can't [music] wait to see me moving
你迫不及待地想看到我随着节拍舞动
[singing] on the beat. Feel my fire
。 感受我燃烧的
heart to breathe. Let's play them
心在呼吸。 让我们播放它们
[singing and music] and rewind the beat.
（歌声和音乐），然后倒放节拍。
Your flesh on the prize they want to be.
你的血肉是他们想要的奖赏。
If you're starving, [music and singing]
如果你饿了，就来听听音乐和歌声，饱餐
come and eat. I'm that girl they want to
一顿吧。 我就是他们想成为的那种女孩，当
when I
我
&gt;&gt; [singing]
唱歌的时候，
&gt;&gt; when I
当我
&gt;&gt; You know you like it when I
你知道你喜欢我唱歌的时候，
You know you like it when I
你知道你喜欢我
[singing]
唱歌的时候，
&gt;&gt; But it ain't rush. It ain't rush. Well,
但这并不着急。 不用着急。 嗯，
well, it ain't rush.
嗯，不用着急。
[__] I got to make my time really rush.
兄弟，我得抓紧时间。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; The kind money we touch. [singing]
我们接触到的那种钱。  [唱歌]
It ain't rush. It ain't rush. Well,
不用着急。 不用着急。 嗯，
well, it ain't rush.
嗯，不用着急。
Nobody hype everybody [singing] they
没人吹捧每个人（唱歌），他们
crush.
碾压一切。   我们这里
There's no darling with us.
没有宝贝。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Hey.
嘿。
&gt;&gt; Let me hear you say go higher go higher
让我听到你们说：再高一点，再高一点，加油！
&gt;&gt; Go higher go higher
再高一点，再高一点，
&gt;&gt; I want to hear you say go higher go
我想听你说再高一点，再高一点。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]再高一点，再高一点
&gt;&gt; higher go.
。
&gt;&gt; Go higher [singing] go higher go.
往高处走 [唱歌] 往高处走。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。   是的
Yeah.
。
See.
看。
Some big guy no they too like dog.
有些身材高大的家伙也喜欢狗。
Animals they in human form. Bad man no
它们是人形的动物。 坏人没
body like work. [music] But you must
人喜欢干活。  [音乐] 但
hustle if you want job.
如果你想找到工作，就必须努力奋斗。
If no finish they want fight [singing]
如果没完没了，他们就想跟我们打架（唱歌）
us. If them they run them no fit catch
。 如果他们跑了，就追不上了
up. I know they come say I too like us.
。 我知道他们会说我也喜欢我们。
No come they come say you too like us.
他们来了，说你们也和我们一样。
Why? Me no get it for the head and the
为什么？ 我感觉不到它，
bad energy come my mind door.
坏能量涌入我的脑门。
&gt;&gt; My mind door.
我的心灵之门。
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh. Make you dance [music] like
嗯哼。 让你像 Olamide 一样跳舞（音乐）。
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Steady green light.
绿灯常亮。
&gt;&gt; Olamide [singing]
Olamide [唱]
&gt;&gt; Steady on my grind no hear what they
稳步前进，不听他们
want telling me good in my mind.
说什么，保持乐观。
[singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Fantasy
幻想
&gt;&gt; See, [music] they want they check if my
，[音乐] 他们想要，他们检查我的
time be the rush. But they didn't hey.
时间是否匆忙。 但他们并没有。
&gt;&gt; It'd be rush [singing] well, well, it'd
唱歌会很匆忙，嗯，会
be much.
很多。
&gt;&gt; Nobody make my time be the rush.
别让我的时间变得匆忙。
The time money we touch.
我们投入的时间和金钱。   是的
Yeah.
。
&gt;&gt; It'd be rush. It'd be rush well, well,
那样太仓促了。 会很匆忙，嗯，
it'd be much. Nobody hype everybody they
会很多。 没人会吹捧那些被他们
crush.
碾压的人。   我们这里
No darling with us.
没有宝贝。   我们这里
&gt;&gt; No [singing] darling with us.
没有爱唱歌的宝贝。   我们这里
Nobody [music] with us.
没有人（音乐）。
Nobody with us.
没有其他人陪着我们。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; So, this is my favorite song to perform,
顺便说一句，这首歌是我最喜欢的表演曲目
by the way.
。
&gt;&gt; Hey.
嘿。
&gt;&gt; So, you have to help me [music] out by
所以，你得跳舞来帮我（演奏音乐）
dancing, eh?
，好吗？
&gt;&gt; Hey.
嘿。
&gt;&gt; I [music] wish kind life where I never
我（音乐）渴望一种我永远不会看到的美好生活
see.
。
I carry God so I fear nothing.
我心中有神，所以我什么都不怕。
Steady increasing [singing] the commas.
逐渐增加逗号的数量（唱出来）。
[music] Why?
[音乐] 为什么？
&gt;&gt; Commas, commas, commas.
逗号，逗号，逗号。
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh.
嗯哼。
Original no be parody.
原作并非戏仿作品。
It no be clear for your memory.
你的记忆可能不太清晰。
Whether na winter or summer. I dey Baba
无论是冬天还是夏天。 我爸爸
don swerve am now.
现在已经避开他了。
&gt;&gt; Living [singing] life to
活着（歌唱）是为了
&gt;&gt; See my [music] fire.
感受我的（音乐）之火。
&gt;&gt; Burning bright.
光芒四射。   他们在
&gt;&gt; Waiting dey [singing] inside me. Small
我心中等待[歌唱]。
way dey mighty. [music] They never know
小路也能强大。  [音乐] 他们永远不会知道
I carry light.
我身上带着光芒。
&gt;&gt; So they don't find
所以他们找不到“
&gt;&gt; Check am balance.
检查余额”这个选项。
&gt;&gt; Everything inside [singing and music]
歌唱和音乐中的一切都
&gt;&gt; My mind dey lead. Trust me. You can't
引领着我的思绪。 相信我。 你
fool me cuz I let you don't got a lot.
骗不了我，因为我让你知道你没多少钱。
&gt;&gt; A lot of us.
我们很多人都是如此。
&gt;&gt; More friendly.
更友善。   我们
&gt;&gt; A [singing] lot of us.
很多人都会唱歌。
&gt;&gt; I'm allergic to
我对
&gt;&gt; So cool. So
So cool 过敏。 所以
&gt;&gt; I'm not ready for
我还没准备好
&gt;&gt; [singing]
唱《
&gt;&gt; No future.
没有未来》。
&gt;&gt; They telling me make I
他们告诉我，我们
&gt;&gt; A lot of us.
很多人都会这样做。
&gt;&gt; Stability on ground now.
目前地面稳定。
Ability now.
现在有能力了。   别提了
&gt;&gt; Don't mention. [singing]
。  [唱歌]
&gt;&gt; I'm not ready for
我还没有准备好迎接
&gt;&gt; No future.
没有未来。
inside life.
生活中总会发生各种各样的事情。
&gt;&gt; Your doubt to make I live my life.
你的疑虑让我无法好好生活。
Dreams [music] come true. If not, fight.
梦想（音乐）成真。 否则，就反抗。
Fight the fight make you no go tire.
战斗让你永不疲倦。
Fire [singing]
火[唱歌]他们
dey go.
走了。
Fire dey go.
火势蔓延。
&gt;&gt; You need to put your body
你需要将你的身体
[singing and music] and soul.
（歌唱和音乐）和灵魂都投入其中。
Leave your worries
把你的忧虑
&gt;&gt; on the Lord.
交给上帝。
&gt;&gt; Baba don swerve am now.
巴巴现在避开他了。
&gt;&gt; Living [singing]
活出[歌唱]
life
人生，
&gt;&gt; See my fire.
看看我的热情。
&gt;&gt; Burning bright.
光芒四射。
&gt;&gt; Oh, waiting dey inside me. Small way dey
哦，它们在我体内等待着。 小路也能
mighty. They never know I carry light.
强大。 他们永远不会知道我身上带着光芒。
&gt;&gt; So they don't find
所以他们找不到“
&gt;&gt; Check am balance.
检查余额”这个选项。
&gt;&gt; Everything inside [music]
音乐中的一切都
&gt;&gt; My mind dey lead. [singing] Trust me.
引领着我的思绪。  [唱歌]相信我。
You can't fool me cuz I let you don't
你骗不了我，因为我让你没
got a
拿到
&gt;&gt; A [music]
A级[音乐]
&gt;&gt; A lot of us.
我们很多人都没有。
&gt;&gt; I'm allergic to
我对
&gt;&gt; So cool. So
So cool 过敏。 所以
&gt;&gt; [singing]
（唱）
&gt;&gt; I'm not ready for
我还没准备好迎接
&gt;&gt; No future.
没有未来。
&gt;&gt; They telling me make I
他们告诉我，我们
&gt;&gt; A lot of us.
很多人都会这样做。
everything now.
现在一切都要稳定。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; No matter the fault.
不管错在哪里。
Now which kind life way I never see? I
我从未见过的那种生活方式是什么？ 我
carry God so I fear nothing. Steady
心中有神，所以我什么都不怕。 逐步
increasing the commands. [singing]
增加指令数量。  [歌唱]
&gt;&gt; [applause and cheering]
[掌声和欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; Make some noise for my amazing band. You
为我超棒的乐队欢呼吧！ 你们
guys sound so good.
唱得真好听。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
[applause]
[掌声]
[music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; So, allow me to take you to church a
那么，请允许我带你们感受一下教堂的氛围
bit, you know.
。
This song is called Army
这首歌叫《Army》，是
my first album.
我第一张专辑里的歌。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[歌唱]
[singing and music]
[歌唱和音乐]
&gt;&gt; Do you really want? Do you really want
你真的想要吗？ 你真的想要
to have it all?
拥有这一切吗？
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Can you really handle it if it comes?
如果真的发生了，你真的能承受得住吗？
Can you really? Can you really? [music]
真的可以吗？ 真的可以吗？  [音乐]
Let's say you have it all. Let's say you
假设你拥有一切。 假设你
have all the things you want. Don't you
拥有了所有你想要的东西。
ever [music] give in to the gods. Don't
音乐，你永远不要向神明屈服。
you ever? Don't you ever?
你从来没有过吗？ 你从来没有过吗？
All the days you're inside, all the
所有你待在家里的日子，所有
times that you prayed inside. Reject
你在屋里祈祷的时刻。
poverty on your [music] side. Reject
在音乐方面，拒绝贫穷。 摒弃
&gt;&gt; poverty [singing]
贫穷（歌唱）
and your mind.
和你的思想。
&gt;&gt; This should be your comfort.
这应该让你感到舒适。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Hope you find your solace.
希望你能找到慰藉。
&gt;&gt; I'm here. I'm here. [singing] I'm here.
我在这里。 我在这里。  [唱歌] 我在这里。
I'm here. I'm here.
我在这里。 我在这里。
&gt;&gt; I'm here.
我在这里。
I'm [singing] here. I'm here.
我在这里唱歌。 我在这里。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Oh my Shelley.
哦，我的雪莱。
Oh my Shelley. [music and singing]
我的天哪，雪莱。  [音乐和歌声]
Oh my wow.
哦，我的天哪。
Every day is just the same.
每天都一样。
No [music] worries for tomorrow.
明天不用担心音乐的事。
I wish I didn't wake today.
我真希望今天没醒来。
But no. [music]
但并非如此。  [音乐]
I got to face my pain.
我必须面对我的痛苦。
I know I've been bad, [singing]
我知道我唱歌不好，
but I'm sorry. [music]
但我很抱歉。  [音乐]
I learned from my mistakes.
我从错误中吸取了教训。
You know what I need.
你知道我需要什么。
I'm waiting for the rain.
我在等下雨。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[歌唱]
&gt;&gt; I'm waiting for my skies to [music] weep
我在等待我的天空再次 [音乐] 哭泣
again.
。
I'm longing every day. [singing]
我每天都在思念。  [唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Mon [music] bébé for the waters.
Mon [音乐] 宝贝，为了水。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I'm making history.
我正在创造历史。
I don't think there's ever [singing]
我认为这一带从来没有像
been any like me from this parts.
我这样的歌手。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I should be happy you like me.
你应该高兴你喜欢我。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; But no.
但是不。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I [singing] know I've been bad, but I'm
我 [唱歌] 我知道我做错了，但我很
sorry. I've learned from my mistakes.
抱歉。 我从错误中吸取了教训。
You know what I need. [music]
你知道我需要什么。  [音乐]
You know what [singing] I need. [music]
你知道我需要什么 [歌唱]。  [音乐]
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[唱歌]
[singing and music]
[唱歌和音乐]
[music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[唱歌]
[cheering]
[欢呼]
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
谢谢。
&gt;&gt; [applause]
[掌声]
[applause and cheering]
[掌声和欢呼声]
[cheering]
[欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; Thank you so much for being here. I
非常感谢你们的到来。 我
appreciate every one of you.
感谢你们每一个人。   祝你有
Have a great day.
美好的一天。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks for watching. Support for NPR
谢谢观看。  NPR
Music comes from Rivian, makers of
Music 得到了 Rivian 的支持，Rivian 是一家生产
all-electric adventure vehicles designed
全电动探险车的公司，其设计充分考虑了
with the planet and future generations
地球和子孙后代的福祉
in mind.
。
A quick update before you go. We're
临走前简单汇报一下情况。 我们将
doing another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter
再次举办 Tiny Desk 赠送活动。 在
by September 12th, 2026 and you and a
2026 年 9 月 12 日之前参加，你和你的
friend could win a free trip to DC to
朋友就有机会赢得前往华盛顿特区的免费旅行，亲临
see a Tiny Desk concert live in [music]
现场观看 Tiny Desk 音乐会
person. You even get to choose which
。 你甚至可以选择
upcoming show you want to see and it's
你想观看的即将上映的节目，而且
completely free to enter. Just go to
完全免费参加。 请访问
npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway.
npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway。
Entering is completely free, but you can
参赛完全免费，但您可以
get more entries by snagging some
通过购买
limited-edition Tiny Desk merch or by
限量版 Tiny Desk 周边商品或
making a special donation to the NPR
向 NPR 网络进行特别捐赠来获得更多参赛机会
network. Learn more and enter today at
。 了解更多信息并立即参加，请访问
npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway.
npr.org/tinydeskgiveaway。